<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: ebenezer | yeah, cheers!]]></title>
  <link href="http://yeahcheers.github.com/blog/categories/ebenezer/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://yeahcheers.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-07-30T18:08:19-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://yeahcheers.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[yeah, cheers!]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Book of Ebenezer le Page]]></title>
    <link href="http://yeahcheers.github.com/blog/2012/07/30/the-book-of-ebenezer-le-page/"/>
    <updated>2012-07-30T12:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://yeahcheers.github.com/blog/2012/07/30/the-book-of-ebenezer-le-page</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2>by G.B. Edwards</h2>

<p>One of the best books I've read, based on nothing other than the fact
that I felt so after reading it. Yes, the ending wavers a bit, as, and
likely for, the reason the introduction hints at, but overall it was
such an authentic piece of writing. Refreshing.</p>

<p>Here are some quotes:</p>

<pre><code>They say children are born because of the love the parents have for each other. I haven't noticed that myself. Perhaps the children are born because the love of the parents for each other is not perfect. Perhaps the children come into the world through a gap between the parents.
</code></pre>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<pre><code>Well, if you want to have wars, you got to have whores.
</code></pre>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<pre><code>'I don't know what a pagan is,' I said, 'so I don't know if I am one or not; but I don't know what a Christian is either. There are thousands of Christians of all shapes and sizes on this island. They may not all of them go after the flesh-pots, though some of them do on the sly; but they go to war and kill other people, and in peace-time make as much money as they can out of each other, and don't love their neighbours any more than I do.'
</code></pre>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<pre><code>The Statue of Liberty is a woman. In fact, she was so good and kind to everybody, I began to wonder if perhaps she didn't like anybody at all really; but only liked being good and kind.
</code></pre>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<pre><code>I see my fellow creatures as trees walking;
</code></pre>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Humpty]]></title>
    <link href="http://yeahcheers.github.com/blog/2012/07/12/humpty/"/>
    <updated>2012-07-12T11:22:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://yeahcheers.github.com/blog/2012/07/12/humpty</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>found raymond's humpty rejoinder to ebenezer's question of why he doesn't return to christine regardless of her vileness, awesome:</p>

<blockquote><p>humpty dumpty sat on a great wall,</p>

<p>humpty dumpty had a great fall,</p>

<p>all the king's horses and all the king's men couldn't put humpty together again</p></blockquote>

<p>perhaps better to just mention the last line, and indirectly invoke the rest, still awesome.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
